# Sricharan Teja Naidu 🔕 Featured

Senior Analyst III seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Client Management, System Analysis, Technical Architecture, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Visual Studio, HTML, CSS, ASP.NET



Current Designation: Senior Analyst III Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Deloitte Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Senior Analyst III, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Client Management, System Analysis, Technical Architecture, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Visual

Studio, HTML, CSS, ASP. NET

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

### Summary

Technically Sophisticated Professional with nearly 7 years of experience in the areas of Software Developing & Programming in ASP.Net MVC MVVM and C#.net Microsoft Technologies. Integrated Twilio SMS service in applications.

Excellent communication skills with experience in coordinating project.

Participated in requirements gathering and analysis and created architectural documentations for applications.

Proficient in developing web and windows based applications using SAFE Agile development technologies and rapid development unit (RDU). SAFE 5.0 certified.

Experienced in developing web applications using ASP.Net, MVC, MVVM, LowCode / No Code, HTML, CSS, JQuery and JavaScript.

Experienced in developing and consuming applications that uses web services/WCF services (Windows communication foundation - 4.0).

Proficient in developing Console applications/windows forms using C#.net

Experienced in developing API's and windows services.

## **Work Experience**

**Deloitte** as Senior Analyst III Oct 2019 to Till Date

TCM- Tax Contraversy Manager OCT 2019 - Present Role: Senior Analyst III (Employer - Deloitte.)

Description of the project

TCM is a web application built on MVVM Design pattern helps tax practicioners to file / store the records of tax forms for that particular audit cycle. They can upload documents where a email service will be triggered when an audit document is created. Reports will be generated for audit cycle records and send to end user by mails using SMPT scheduled service. Mobile messages will be send to the end users using Twilio SMS service.

**Wells Fargo EGS** as Apps System Engineer Aug 2018 to Oct 2019

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=60e30bb8247b79a243210346290716cd0b0b0100431b5b475716465d5...

PAICE - Print Audit Information

AUG 2018 - OCT 2019

Collection Engine

Role: Application Developer (Employer - Wells Fargo EGS ltd)

Description of the project:

PAICE is intended to discover all printers on the retail stores network and then feed the data to HP site. The EUC group has a new initiative to outsource some of the retail stores printer management functions to HP for 23000 plus devices.

### Tata Consultancy Services as System Engineer

Feb 2014 to Jul 2018

British Telecom - Wholesale

FEB 2014 - JUL 2018

Online Ordering System

Role: Application Developer (Employer - TCS Itd)

Description of the project:

British telecom - Wholesale is the Europe's largest wholesale communications business by revenue and market. Its business serves fixed and mobiles service providers, internet service providers, communications services resellers and global broadcasters and TV production companies with the widest range of services available from a wholesale provider, regionally or nationally in the UK or across 170 countries worldwide. It offer a wide range of products such as broadband, voice, cloud services and services on traditional, next generation and IP based networks.

As a part of this project, we have developed two applications. One is an online website, through which the resellers can order products like PSTN lines, SIP Trunking, mobile numbers etc. The other being a console application, where the resellers can call the BT agents, and place their orders. Both of these applications, allows the resellers to place orders on behalf of their customers using our application. It provides the user to configure their product, calculate pricing, allows modifying their product configuration once the product is delivered, ceasing or ending the product contract. The application also allows the customer to raise tickets/faults if the product delivered does not work as per his expectation or if the service does not work as expected.

#### Responsibilities:

Involved in requirement analysis and application design, experienced in coordinating with multiple teams.

Currently working in Devops culture which is the future of any software developer.

Involved in creation of technical documentation for application designs.

Worked closely with the end customers in fixing the issues of live application.

Involved in creating prototypes for new products that are yet to be launched.

Development of web application using ASP.net, C#.net, MVC, MVVM and Visual studio.

Involved in code review and performance tuning.

Working as lead developer for an year. Responsible for development, maintenance and support of the applications.

Served as the lead for UI revamp team.

Cross browser compatible development and testing for various versions of IE (8, 9, 10, and 11), Safari, Chrome, Edge, EdgeChromium and Firefox.

Worked on creation of unit test cases.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from G Pulla Reddy Engineering College, Kurnool in 2013

#### **Affirmative Action**

**Work Authorization** 

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time